hey guys welcome to another crash course
video this time for chamia chamia is the
new Havoc DPS so let's just get straight
into it so for now I'll just go through
her basic combo chains she has two forms
so I'll just call this form White chamia
and the other form red chamia and this
is her combo chain so you simply press
basic attack like
this and she goes into the
spin however you can press and hold the
spin to extend it like this 1 2 3 four
hold
spin
release and she can access this spin via
combo three or combo four or straight
out from heavy attack so if I press and
hold basic attack like this she goes
straight into a
spin and the good thing about this spin
is that it will actually Parry all
incoming attacks now for holding an
attack after the third combo 1 two
3 and then hold
it or hold it after the fourth combo so
one two three four that's the full
one just like
that as for a plch attack it's simple no
other gimmicks about
it now let's talk about red chamia it's
called The Blossom State and you simply
access this by pressing her resonance
skill so press e and she goes into
suspended form and her basic attack
chain will be different so if I press
basic it'll look like
this a wider spin you can also hold hold
this simply by pressing basic and then
hold or you can simply just hold the
entire basic attack button from start to
finish and she will do all three combo
sequences on her own so if I press and
hold right now she does it like this you
don't have to spam basic at
all so it has a wider AOE on this spin
but the downside to this form is that
you can really move it's less mobile if
you really want to move around you got
to press Dodge and pressing jump or
pressing resonance skill will cancel
this form so if I press
jump she reverts back to white white
chamia or resonance skill now if I press
resonance skill same thing resonance
skill reverts one thing to note is that
her e skill can also be used in the air
like
this so if you really want to stay in
this form indefinitely what you can do
is press jump and then press e
so that you stay in this form remember
when you press jump it's just going to
cancel her form revert back to normal
but you can press e again resonance
skill and then she's back here so one
thing to note is that when she's
suspended in the air you can see that
her stamina is constantly draining using
attacks also drain the stamina but it's
at a really really slow rage so it
shouldn't be a problem at
all now let me cancel this by jumping
back to White chamia
so now you got the gist of it basically
you can just press and hold basic if you
want and to go spin see she's just a
spin to win character so I'll spare you
all the details all you need to know for
chamia is just spin spin in
normal go into
red spin in this form as well it's all
spinning just like that and then either
jump or resonance skill to cancel out of
this form
like
that now let's talk about her forte I
will cut to the Chase and Skip all the
wall attacks tool tips I'll just list
out the steps here all you need to know
is that step one perform an intro attack
step two is to spend the gauge and the
only way to do that is by simply
attacking every attack except for
resonance Liberation except for Ultimate
Will consume the gauge and the more
Forte gauge you consume the more conto
you get and also the more damage bonus
you will get later on so from the top
step one intro step two finish up the
gauge doing every attack except for
ultimate step three will be the state
that I am in right now with empty gauge
and also full conero with her enhanced
resonance skill ready and after doing
her enhanced resonance skill she will go
into this state called budding mode
where all her damage except for ultimate
will be increased by 50% up to 100%
depending on the number of uh Forte
gauge you've consumed okay hopefully
you've been following so far it's
actually simpler than it looks except
that the tool tip makes it look
complicated than it is so I'll go over
from the top again we'll start off with
intro so I'll start with
Verina now that she's full intro
Chamilia and she'll have a full gauge
like this just Spam any attack spam all
her attacks spam e spam your spam your
spin see how the gauge is draining and
now it's full empty gauge with 10 Stacks
e is glowing press
e it's a
nuke and then same thing span span it
all this is basically her nuke face free
damage and that's how you play
her okay so from the top again first
intro chamia in her gauge will be full
spam all her skills resonance skill her
spinning attack to empty the gauge once
the gauge is empty wait for your conero
to be full once conero is full her e
skill will be glowing press that skill
she will do a nuke and then she will go
into an enhanced State more damage and
you repeat the same thing again spam her
spin spam e skill until it's empty as
for her ultimate it's similar to giny
where it doesn't do anything else except
that it does free free damage and also
gives you conto it'll act as an Certo
battery and I can bring her in again
intro is full again do the same thing
again finish the
gaug and then get
conto press
e same thing during this form spam
everything so TLD drr to play chamia to
be honest before I release this guide
you're probably already playing her
correctly it's simply pressing the
buttons when they light up that's about
it switch her in full gauge spam all the
attacks until her e is glowing press the
glowing e and then spam all the attacks
and then use ultimate whenever it's
available and then switch her out that's
it for chamia now you're a master of
playing chamia so one cool thing is that
if you want to travel with chamia in her
red form all you need to do is is press
uh grapple while in this form like this
and then you can run with her but then
uh dodging and jumping will cancel it
see like that now let's talk about her
gear and skills for her weapon obviously
her signature weapon is the best if you
don't have it like me on my f2p account
you can just use Emerald of Genesis it's
also really formidable because it gives
crit rate as well and the effects for it
is also decent Chang's signature weapon
is also fine for her otherwise the BP
fourstar weap weapon is also good
otherwise just use any attack based
weapon for her really straightforward
for weapon as for her Echo you can opt
for 43311 configuration or 44111 with
both crownless and dreamless and
depending on the weapon that you have
the usual for the four cost you go
either crit rate or crit damage to
balance your one to2 crit rate and crit
damage ratio for the three cost you can
just go double element or element and
attack so either double Havoc or havoc
and attack the differences are
negligible and of course one cost will
be attack and attack as for substats
it's also the usual both crit rate crit
damage for substats attack percent or
flat attack energy regen and basic
attack so Chamilia scales off basic
attack you want basic attack damage if
you can help it for her skill leveling
priority I'll just give it straight to
you level everything except for intro if
you're resource strap you need both
normal attack resonance skill Forte
because Normal attack and resonance
skill both has her spin damage and Forte
is that nuke that she has and Liberation
for obvious reasons it's free damage so
these four are priority and everything
else across the board up here intro
having a lower priority for the same
obvious reasons and that's basically it
so level everything everything pretty
much intro being last for her resonance
change sequences Chamilia is already
playable at s0 so if you already have
one copy of her that's enough as far as
her gameplay goes because all of her
other sequences are just numbers it just
increases her damage so S1 is not that
important casting intro gives her
critical damage increase and also immune
to Interruption when she does her forte
explosion S2 is the first stopping point
where that explosion damage is increased
by 120% for the damage multiplier and
then S3 is the next stopping point where
ultimate damage is increased by 50% and
her attack is increased by whooping 58%
during budding mode budding mode is that
state she's in after using her enhanced
e skill resonance skill and after that
S4 and S5 are not that good as far as
cost go S4 is basic attack bonus for the
party S5 is an outro and intro skill
buff so there's a mistake in the
translation here it's actually intro
skill increased by 33% and outro skill
is increased by 68% and then S6 tldr of
S6 is that you get an extra charge of
her special enhanced e skill after doing
it so you can explode twice and also a
massive damage increase when she's in
that enhanced state to put it simply her
stopping point are s0 S2 S3 and then S6
you want to skip S1 S4 and five so 2 3 6
or keep it at zero team composition wise
straightforward the first character that
you start with is the Healer so either
shke keeper or Vina and the best second
character for her is sanoa because San
Buffs basic attack so San is going to
immensely increase her damage with her
outro basic buff and then chamia their
Echo set obviously short keeper or
Verina goes healing set sanua will go
moonlit set and then Chamilia can either
go lingering Tunes set or the Havoc set
up to you lingering Tunes is also good
for outro but most people usually roll
with havoc and one last thing for the
forecast between crownless and dreamless
if you have questions about it dreamless
and crownless they're both fine
crownless gives you the ability to get
the Havoc damage increased by simply
transforming to it and Dodge cancelling
like this
this and then you can go about your day
and of course dreamless for even more
damage free damage and also resonance
Liberation charge and yeah that's about
it for camia's crash course I think this
is about as crash course as it gets
hopefully this video has helped you in
understanding on how to play her you're
already most likely playing her
correctly it's just uh spin spam Spin
and then press glowy buttons and that's
about it all right see you take care
bye-bye